score.org 2010-12-02

# Privacy Policy | SCORE

|  |  |   
---  
This privacy statement describes what we do with the information that we receive about you when you visit our Web site. The information that we receive about you depends on what you do when you visit our Web site.  
If you visit our site to browse, or to read or download information (ALL VISITORS):  
  
We automatically receive information about the computer that you are using, including IP address, browser software, operating system, and the name of the domain and host from which you access the Internet. We also record the date and time you access our site and the Internet address of the Web site from which you linked directly to our site. 

We use this information to send you a "cookie" when you visit our Web site. A cookie is a file that identifies you as a unique user. We use cookies to track the number of people visiting our Web site ([www.score.org](http://www.score.org/)).  
  
If you request email counseling:  
  
We receive your name, email address and zip code when you submit your request. We also receive any other personal information that you provide in the text of your email request.

We use your name and email address to respond to your request for business counseling. We use your zip code to identify the general area in which you live so that we can monitor the geographical scope and impact of our services and also so that we can provide counseling appropriate for your location. The SCORE counselor that receives your email request will have access to other personal information that you provide in the text of your email request. The SCORE counselor will keep this information confidential but may consult with other SCORE counselors about your situation in order to better serve you.         
  
If you sign up for a SCORE email newsletter:  
  
We receive your name, state, zip code, email address and various other general information that you might choose to provide about yourself or your business. 

We use your name and email address to deliver the email newsletter, updates or announcements that you have requested ( _SCORE eNews_ , _SCORE Expert Answers_ ). 

Although SCORE newsletters, updates or announcements may contain occasional links or references to various SCORE commercial partners, these links and references do not mean that we rent, sell or otherwise disseminate to commercial partners information that we receive about you.  

You can be removed from a mailing list at any time by sending a message to [webmaster@score.org](mailto:webmaster@score.org) with the word “unsubscribe” in the subject line.   
  
If you submit a testimonial or success story:  
  
We receive your name, place of business and email address as well as the information that you submit (your testimonial or success story).

At our discretion, we may display on our site your testimonial or success story, including personal information that you provide as part of your testimonial submission.    
  
Security  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. In order to prevent unauthorized access to your information, we have instituted safeguards such as physical access restrictions, software defenses and written guidelines instructing volunteers on the confidentiality of your personal information. We have also implemented safeguards to notify us in the event of loss of Internet connectivity. Even with these safeguards in place, unauthorized access, loss of connectivity or hardware failure can still occur. For this reason, we cannot guarantee that our safeguards will be totally effective all of the time nor can we be responsible for lost or delayed requests, email, or content that may result from loss of connectivity or other technical failures.  
Children’s Privacy  
We are concerned about protecting children’s privacy. We do not anticipate that children will be visitors or users of our Web site, email counseling, or other services. We do not knowingly collect personal contact information, online or offline, from children under the age of 13 and will not do so when we learn or suspect that such information is being provided by a child even if the stated age is 13 or over.
